=== NoMoreCaptchas ===
Contributors: oxfordbio
Tags: spam, captcha, buddypress, registration, login, comments
Requires at least: 3.0
Tested up to: 3.9
Stable tag: 1.2.2
License: GPLv2 or later

NoMoreCaptchas keeps spam bots out of your site and only allows human beings to register or login without annoying Captcha codes or faulty blacklists.

== Description ==

NoMoreCaptchas puts an end to annoying Captcha codes that send away many users and authenticates human beings based on the one thing that can never be faked - their behavior. 

Developed at Oxford University, this technology uses bio-chronometric markers that cannot be copied. They are created when a person interacts with almost any modern computing device that can accept human-initiated input. 

Since its behavior that's being examined, there's no whitelist, blacklist or roadblocks for users - just easy access for all human beings. And that means the end of the road for spam bots.

Installation is simple and you con monitor it working through your own personal dashboard. Just register, download and install and see it work.

== Installation ==

NoMoreCaptchas Installation Guide
Installing NoMoreCaptchas is very simple. All you need is the plugin and a License Key. Here's how you do it:

1: Register  
Register on http://www.NoMoreCaptchas.com/register to receive your License Key and download link. Make sure you accept the terms and conditions!
An email will be sent to you within seconds once you submit your registration. Be sure to save that email.

2: Download  
When you register, you will receive an email with your License Key and a download link. Click on the link to download the plugin ZIP file.
If you already downloaded the plugin from the WordPress store, there is no need to download it again.

3: Add New Plugin  
Go to your website's WordPress Dashboard and click on
Plugins> Add New

4: Upload & Install  
Select Upload at the top left of the screen, then click on Browse. Navigate to where you saved the NoMoreCaptchas plugin. Select the plugin package (the complete ZIP file) and click on Open.
Click on Install Now and WordPress will automatically install the plugin.

5: Activate  
Once WordPress has successfully installed the NoMoreCaptchas plugin, click on Activate. You will then automatically be redirected to the plugin page.

6: Enter Your License Key  
The email you received when you registered contains your License Key.
Go to Settings> NoMoreCaptchas in your WordPress dashboard.
Copy your License Key to the License Key field.

7: Validate  
Click on Validate License Key. You will see the fields fill in with your registration information.
You will also see your Authentication Code. You will need this and your domain name in order to access your Customer Dashboard to see NoMoreCaptchas in action.

8: Sit Back, Relax and Enjoy the Best Bot Protection There Is!
There's nothing else you need to do. NoMoreCaptchas is now protecting your login and registration pages from spambots and will make sure you only interact with real human beings!


== Frequently Asked Questions ==

= What makes NoMoreCaptchas different? = 

We don't use traditional Captcha, or problem-solving methods to make a user prove he or she is human. Most people find that annoying – and user studies show that 74% of the time, people will abandon a site that makes them solve a Captcha code. 
We also don't use blacklists and whitelists to cross check users. Those databases are as fallible as the humans who maintain them and can be wrong. And if you're the one who has been accidentally listed as spam, Spamhaus and the other 5 leading spam databases have a long, opaque procedure for getting yourself off of them. It's a frustrating experience. And even if you're fine, cross-checking database lists creates a lag for the user.
With the biochronometric technology in NoMoreCaptchas, users don't need to do  anything but be themselves. Our analytics know faster than they do whether they're human or bots.
As a matter of fact, we don't ask users to do anything at all. Instead, we use our advanced biochronometric technology to analyze In , 2  factor device authentication, the Company has devised unique signatures based on hundreds of individual inputs of users of both mobile and traditional desk top computing devices, allowing for BioChronometric authentication and authorization on virtually all current available devices.  The algorithms, protected by trade secrets and patents pending, can't currently be replicated by humans or bots, creating passive, always on security for all on line applications.

= What exactly is biochronometric protection? = 
Bio means life and chrono means time. We devised unique signatures based to determine whether someone is acting alive over time based on hundreds of individual user inputs that people automatically generate just simply by being alive. The time we need to figure out if you're alive or a bot is just fractions of a second. And since bots can't fake being alive, we can be sure we block them and let only real humans enjoy your site.

= Is NoMoreCaptchas a 508-compliant solution? =
Yes. Section 508 of the Americans with Disabilities Act (ADA) requires websites to be built in such a way that the blind, visually impaired and others with disabilities are able to use the site without issue. Most Captcha solutions are very difficult for those with visual impairments – and the audio solutions are a clumsy workaround at best.
Since NoMoreCaptchas doesn't require users to do anything but be human, the path is made equally accessible to everyone.

= How can I tell if NoMoreCaptchas is working? =
Seeing NoMoreCaptchas in action is believing, and there's no better place to see it happen than your Dashboard, located at http://nomorecaptchas.com/customer-dashboard/. If you have a free version of NoMoreCaptchas, you'll see the last 400 actions. If you're one of your subscribers (thanks!) you'll be able to customize your view.

To log in to your NoMoreCaptchas Dashboard, visit the Customer Dashboard page (http://nomorecaptchas.com/customer-dashboard/) and enter your Authenticating Code and the domain you registered. 

= Is NoMoreCaptchas compatible with BuddyPress? =
Yes. We have tested it up to the latest release (BuddyPress 2.0) and it is compatible.

= Which pages does NoMoreCaptchas protect? =
NoMoreCaptchas prevents spambots from registering or logging in to your site. So the login page is protected and, if you use BuddyPress' registration page, that is also protected.

In other words, it protects the pages where you would normally place a Captcha code.

= What do I need to install NoMoreCaptchas? =
Installing NoMoreCaptchas is easy. All you need are the plugin zip file and your License Key.

To get your License Key, register your site with us at http://nomorecaptchas.com/register/. As soon as you do, we'll send you a license key and a unique download link.

Registering allows us to create a unique key for your site that will make your NoMoreCaptchas keeps spam bots away and only allows humans through the door.


= I'm still getting spam, what's happening? =
If NoMoreCaptchas is properly installed (see above) and you are able to see your dashboard, there are a few possible issues:

You may not have registered. If you believe you did (or if you're a subscriber, if know you are up to date on your payment but are not listed as active), please contact us at support@nomorecaptchas.com
If that's not the case, then your License Key was not properly entered into the control panel. Please be sure to copy and paste it directly from the email we sent you. If you no longer have your License Key, please contact us at support@nomorecaptchas.com so we can send you a new one.
There may have been some spam registrations pending in your queue. Please make sure you have eliminated anyone who got in before you installed NoMoreCaptchas.
The only other reason you might be getting spam is if an actual human decided to register on your site and spam you personally. Believe it or not, some people have that kind of time on their hands. That's not the way most spammers operate, so it's probably someone you recently beat in a game of WoW or didn't like something you said on Reddit.
